Alright, we've introduce forward rolling.
So let's continue along that vein.
The principle of rolling is that of a ball, meaning you roll a ball.
A ball rolls rather redundant.
Needless to say, on this the things you have to be very aware of is you have to be aware of where your hips are.
A very common issue, a very common problem that people encounter is that when they're rolling they have a tendency to lose that structure.
And to lose the inner-abdominal strength.
And so it causes the hip to flop, and you get a hip that lands hard or the feet fly out.
Things happen, people get hurt, you twist the back or something.
Those are the most common injuries to occur.
So you have to maintain and you have to be completely and totally aware that when you are forward rolling, hands are down, stand up, make sure that there's inner-abdominal strength and stability in this area.
Okay.
So always roll, it's always a ball, it's always form and fashion of a ball.
The function of a ball.
So, now I mean it's not complex, but it doesn't feel very good when you mess it up.
So, one more time.
Forward roll, you should come up to the exact same position you started at, for right now.